Kheel, Theodore W. Audio-Visual Materials 6021 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- McGeorge School - Class #6 -- Political Aspects of Communications Law, 12 (Box 20)
- Sandy Duncan Remote w/Virginia Woodruff, 13 (Box 20)
- McGeorge School Compilation Tape / w Morton Hamburg, 14 (Box 20)
- Color Plus - The Professional Plus, 15 (Box 20)
- T. Kheel, 1 (Box 21)
  1.Collective Bargaining, Session #10; 2.Collective Bargaining Session #2
- TWK, Collective Bargaining, 2 (Box 21)
  1.Session#2; 2.Session #3
- TWK Collective Bargaining, 3 (Box 21)
  Session #2 continued
- TW Kheel -- 9/23, Pt. 2, 4 (Box 21)
- T Kheel, Collective Barg., 5 (Box 21)
  1.Session #4; 2.Session #6
- T. Kheel, Collective Barg., 6 (Box 21)
  1.Session #3
- TW Kheel, Collective Bargaining, Session #6 (pt. 3), 7 (Box 21)
- The Institute of collective Bargaining Labor Looks at the 80's; The J.P. Stevens Agreement / Jack Sheinkman, 8 (Box 21)
- What's Happening America? Sharon Alexander, Host #176, 9 (Box 21)
- T. Kheel, Collective Barg. Session #10 (part 1), 10 (Box 21)
- 1.The Suisway - Mark Lindquist; 2.DEI, 3-D animation; 3.Video palette, Demo reel, 11 (Box 21)
- Demo Tape 1980, 12 (Box 21)
- Herman Cooper, B-day - Re-Ted Kheel, 1980, 13 (Box 21)
- Secret Horror by Michael Smith, 14 (Box 21)
- CNB-TV Copy -- Kanachi by Solaris, 15 (Box 21)
  produced by S. Lawrence / M. Owen with H. Smith
- Video Communication Resources -- Levy/Silver - Phillie/Washington, 16 (Box 21)
  Reel #12 (tape 1)
- Collective Barg. #6 -- Kheel/Hudson, 17 (Box 21)
- The Accounting of video - Enhart, 18 (Box 21)
- Opinions an Accounting of Video, 1 (Box 22)
- Sylvia, 2 (Box 22)
- TW Kheel - Collective Bargaining Session #6 (pt.4); Session #8 (pt.1) partial recording?, 3 (Box 22)
- T. Kheel - Collective Bargaining - 1.Session #4 (cont.), 4 (Box 22)
- Democratic National Convention - 8/11/1980 -- Reel I, 5 (Box 22)
- Election Night - Live - 11/4/1980, 6 (Box 22)
  Dub -- Reel #1
- ICB - Labor Looks at the 80's -- JP Stevens/Jack Sheinkman, 7 (Box 22)
- To Bare Witness; part two -- Gabe Pressman, 8 (Box 22)
- Production Plus, 9 (Box 22)
  hold for re-use
- Susan Byers; Interview #9, Documentary Internship, 10 (Box 22)
- Jerome Mora Interview #1, 11 (Box 22)
- Pams #2; Doug Davis, Double Entendre, 12 (Box 22)
- Election Night Live Promo - 10/17/1980, 13 (Box 22)
- Great Image - ATN - Windows of the World - Pfaelzer Bros, 14 (Box 22)
  Original Edited Master
- New Yorker Magazine - Compilation of Commercials, 15 (Box 22)
- Kelber: 11/24, 12/1, 12/2, 12/3, 12/8 Final Session, 16 (Box 22)
- Kheel: 11/18; Kelber: 11/19; Cohen: 11/20 & 22, 17 (Box 22)
- Kheel #1 -- 9/16/1980, 18 (Box 22)
- Collective Barg. Session #4, 19 (Box 22)
- Double Entendre, 1 (Box 23)
  Official Master Edit
- Canadian Anti-Smoking Ads, 2 (Box 23)
- Interview with Irving Bluestone, 3 (Box 23)
- Spin Cut 2; Nothing But a Shoe, Cut 1, 4 (Box 23)
  i-productions
- Jell Conference (shootings), 5 (Box 23)
- Collective Bargaining Session #3, 6 (Box 23)
- Kheel, Kelber, Session #11, 7 (Box 23)
- Kheel: 10/21, 8 (Box 23)
- Kheel - 9/20/1980, Met. Strike, 9 (Box 23)
- Kheel - 9/23, 10 (Box 23)
- Kheel: 10/28; 11/11, 11 (Box 23)
- Kheel, Hadson, Michelson - #10, 12 (Box 23)
- Kheel: 10/7, 13 (Box 23)
- To Bare Witness, Gabe Pressman, 14 (Box 23)
  Dub -- part one
- Robert Milli, 15 (Box 23)
- Nellie Bellflower, 16 (Box 23)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 24)
- Stock Market Observer, June 5, 1969 - Theodore W. Kheel appearance, 2 (Box 24)
- Unlabeled, 3 (Box 24)
- Red Orchestra - Cornered Night Sea -- 1/31/1980, 4 (Box 24)
- Unlabeled, 5 (Box 24)
- American Cancer Society - voice over/Breast Self Examination Segment; Doctor Leffal & Dr. Holleb. -- Feb. 6, 1980, 6 (Box 24)
- Ass't. Music, 7 (Box 24)
- V.O. Opening Montage - 3/22/1983; Show #9, L.A. Task Force - Ft. Lee New Jersey, World Pop. Song Festival, 8 (Box 24)
- CNB-TV Promo. Dialogue track, 9 (Box 24)
- Music 15, 10 (Box 24)
- V.O. Judy - June 6, 1983; Show #4 - (Tease) Close; V.O. Beyond the Horizon, 11 (Box 24)
- JWT/6/6/1980, 12 (Box 24)
- OMS Teleconference - Reel II, 13 (Box 24)
- OMS Teleconference Reel I, 14 (Box 24)
- V.O. Marugo "Travel Show" #8; V.O. Qualiy Control Show #6, 15 (Box 24)
- Unlabeled, 16 (Box 24)
  new?
- CNB - Vo intro Music Festival, 17 (Box 24)
- Kheel Courses, 18 (Box 24)
- Unlabeled, 19 (Box 24)
- Theodore W. Kheel seminar - 12/5/1974 - Public Employment, 1 (Box 25)
- Kheel Course - Sixth session - 3/6/1975; 1/2 of fifth session, 2 (Box 25)
- 5/1/1975, 3 (Box 25)
- Unlabeled, 4 (Box 25)
- 6/5/1975 - ICB Course, 5 (Box 25)
- Kheel Course #3; Second Seminar session - Nov. 6, 1974, 6 (Box 25)
- Kheel Course #1, 7 (Box 25)
- Unlabeled, 8 (Box 25)
- Unlabeled, 9 (Box 25)
- Kheel Course #2 -- Second half of first course session, 10 (Box 25)
- Kheel Course session #4, 11 (Box 25)
- TWK Course - 4th Session, 12 (Box 25)
- folder 1: Sunset Crater (Box 26)
  - Sunset Crater, 1 (Box 26)
  - Mass - print #8, 1 (Box 40)
  - Roy Wilkins: the Right to Dignity, 1 (Box 41)
  - Careers in Carpentry / United Brotherhood of Carpenters &&; Joiners of America, 1 (Box 42)
  - Monex: the Monsoon Experiment - print #2, 1 (Box 43)
  - After Our Baby Died - print reel #2, 1 (Box 44)
  - I Wish I Knew How It Would Feel To Be Free, 1 (Box 45)
  - I'm a Man -- print #22, 1 (Box 46)
- folder 1: Sesame Street Goes to Prison -- print #6 (Box 27)
  - Sesame Street Goes to Prison -- print #6, 1 (Box 27)
  - First Dive, Last Dive, 1 (Box 52)
  - Not For Ourselves Alone, 1 (Box 53)
  - The Global Weather Experiment - Showprint, 1 (Box 54)
  - Sing Joyfully -- Answer Print from AB rolls, 1 (Box 55)
- folder 1: Unlabeled -- Shipped to Steve Lawrence, CBS, from R.J. Kalaski (Box 28)
  - Unlabeled, 1 (Box 28)
  - NOAA "The Seventh Service", 1 (Box 56)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 29)
- Labor Looks at the Delegates - 5/29/1981, 2 (Box 29)
- CNB - TV Promo -- 60 Minutes, 3 (Box 29)
- News Forum - 5/6/1983, 4 (Box 29)
- News Forum - 4/29/1983, 5 (Box 29)
- Hay Associates - Opinions, 1 (Box 30)
  Emhart Prod. Master
- Tape 1 - Rauschenberg Exhibit - Tele Japan #10, 2 (Box 30)
- Unlabeled, 3 (Box 30)
- Full Count Productions - In Another League - 6/23/1983, 4 (Box 30)
- Canister with 2 rolls of video (small rolls) - Unlabeled, 1 (Box 31)
- St. Johns Univ. Press Conference - "Photo Contest" Automation House - 6/1/1983, 2 (Box 31)
- Beyond the Horizon - Work Reel, 3 (Box 31)
- Kheel Spot - "Bond Issue-NO", 4 (Box 31)
- Bound Feet, 1 (Box 32)
- Charisma Alive and Well - 8/26/1981 -- "Opening Animation", 2 (Box 32)
- American Cancer Society, 3 (Box 32)
  Back up master (with D.S. Key) - tape #2
- Work Reel - Talking Head, 4 (Box 32)
- Theodore Kheel v. William F. Buckley Jr. - Firing Line - The Police Civilian Complaint Review board, Oct. 7, 1966, 5 (Box 32)
- CPR Institute for Dispute Resolution - What's the Alternative, 6 (Box 32)
- CPR Institute for Dispute Resolution - Mediation in Action, 7 (Box 32)
- CPR Institute for Dispute Resolution - Out of Court: the Minitrial, 8 (Box 32)
- Unlabeled (Box 33)
- Muse Underwater Video - Compilation Tape - 2001, 1 (Box 34)
- If You Don't come in Sunday, Don't Come in Monday, 2 (Box 34)
- NUL President Hugh B. Price, The National Press Club, Newsmakers Luncheon, December 10, 1999 -- "The Aim of Education Standards: Victors, Not Victims", 3 (Box 34)
- American Arbitration Association - 2001 Annual Meeting, 4 (Box 34)
- Grace Hunt, 5 (Box 34)
- Movie Watch, Oct. 18., 1976, 6 (Box 34)
- Brun Schwig & FILS -- 12/8/1983 -- Fabric/Logo Shots, 7 (Box 34)
- TVB - Edit -- 8/24/1983 -- BUUP mat'l., 8 (Box 34)
- This is New York - 4/22/1948 -- TW Kheel interviewed by Bill Leonard - pt. 1&2, 1 (Box 35)
- This is New York - 4/22/1948 -- TW Kheel interviewed by Bill Leonard - pt. 3, 2 (Box 35)
- Unlabeled, 3 (Box 35)
- I-IV (only labeling), 4 (Box 35)
- II-V (only labeling), 5 (Box 35)
- III-IV (only labeling), 6 (Box 35)
- Oil Barge Strike Settlement; pt.1-2 - Jan. 3, 1948 -- City of New York Municipal Broadcasting System, 7 (Box 35)
- Oil Barge Strike Settlement; pt. 1-2 -- Jan. 3, 1948, 8 (Box 35)
  c.2 - Scratched
- Theodore Kheel Interview - NYC Central Labor Council - (1 of 3) (Box 36.1)
  - Theodore Kheel Interview - NYC Central Labor Council - 3 discs, 1 (Box 36)
- Theodore Kheel Interview - NYC Central Labor Council - (2 of 3) (Box 36.2)
- Theodore Kheel Interview - NYC Central Labor Council - (3 of 3) (Box 36.3)
- Theodore Kheel, Michael Brizel on Collective Bargaining in Football (Box 37)
  - Theodore Kheel, Michael Brizel on Collective Bargaining in Football, 1 (Box 37)
- Back of the Book Shows 1 & 2 - 6/3/1983, 1 (Box 38)
- TVB Tape 3, 2 (Box 38)
  Master Spectrum
- Bump-Up Footage #1 -- Sheridan Elser, 3 (Box 38)
- Smore-Less, 1 (Box 39)
- Kheel Course 2 - Nov. 6, 1974, 2 (Box 39)
- Unlabeled, 3 (Box 39)
- Kheel - ICB Course I - 10/3/1974 - Part II, 4 (Box 39)
- Dr. Charles Moore, 5 (Box 39)
- Louisville - 8/20 - Roll 4 -- Mall, Wesley House, School of Dance, 1976; 6 (Box 39)
  Show #4, Sunday, Oct. 17, 1976 -- Master
- Print #8 "Mass" (Box 40)
- Roy Wilkins: the Right to Dignity (Box 41)
- The Global Weather Experiment -- Showprint (Box 42)
- Monex: the Monsoon Experiment - print #2 -- P. Rosen prods. (Box 43)
- After Our Baby Died - print reel #2 -- Peter Rosen Prods. (Box 44)
- I Wish I Knew How it Would Feel to be Free (Box 45)
- I'm a Man -- print #22 (Box 46)
- Seniority vs. Ability (Box 47)
  - Seniority vs. Ability, 1 (Box 47)
  - Speaking Freely, 1 (Box 48)
  - Unlabeled, 1 (Box 33)
  - Unlabeled, 1 (Box 49)
  - Four for the future, 1 (Box 50)
  - Reflections: Samuel Eliot Morison, 1 (Box 51)
- Speaking Freely (Box 48)
- unlabeled (Box 49)
- Four for the future (Box 50)
- Reflections: Samuel Eliot Morison (Box 51)
- First Dive, Last Dive (Box 52)
- Not For Ourselves Alone (Box 53)
- Careers in Carpentry / United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners of America (Box 54)
- Sing Joyfully -- Answer Print from AB rolls (Box 55)
- folder 2: NOAA "The Seventh Service - Ans. Pt. A - Show Print (Box 56)